[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Our camp is just up ahead.
Turn right at that intersection
and we're there.
Slow down.
It's just ahead.
This is my home.
Mom!
Cheng Ren!
Your leg...
How... How did this happen?
It hurts so much.
Quick, get inside! Hurry!
[Apocalypse Log 7]
After your father died,
it's just been the two of us.
If something happens to you,
what will I do?
We have no food and no medicine.
This wretched place...
We can't survive here much longer.
And now you're...
Mom.
Don't cry.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault for being useless.
I couldn't catch any game,
and I even got myself injured.
I'm a burden to you.
Madam.
Please don't cry.
We injured him by mistake.
We will take full responsibility.
We'll be staying here for a while.
You've seen how things are here.
If you don't help us,
a widow and her son
really won't be able to survive.
Don't worry.
We'll go out for food tomorrow.
It's too late today.
There are some biscuits in the bag.
Have some to tide you over.
How long have you lived here?
Are there any zombies nearby?
It's been a while.
Since we arrived, we haven't seen any zombies.
It's very safe here.
Come with me.
Our space is limited.
One person can sleep here.
But it needs to be tidied up.
There's a shed outside.
One more person can sleep there.
This place will do.
He can...
He'll sleep with me.
It's okay, madam.
I'll sleep here.
You should rest early. Don't worry about us.
It shouldn't take too long.
I think we can leave in a few days.
There's no hurry.
You're actually not in a hurry to leave?
You saw the boat, right?
I'll check the boat's condition tomorrow.
We'll take the waterway once it's fixed.
You're not sleeping yet?
You go to sleep first.
What are you two doing?
Don't worry, madam.
We'll come back with food.
The hull is mostly intact.
The fuel tank is empty.
The wires are also broken.
If we can find wires and diesel,
we should be able to fix it.
Then let's go look for them.
You still want to eat that?
I'm not stupid.
Last time was truly an accident.
If you don't go looking for trouble,
there won't be any accidents.
Mount Zhiliao.
This waterway leads back to our old camp.
How's it going on your end?
I found some usable wires.
That's everything. Let's go.
You're back.
You must be tired after a long day.
I just made some soup.
I picked some wild vegetable leaves outside.
Have a sip to quench your thirst.
I'm not thirsty.
Neither of us is thirsty.
Madam, you and your son have it.
My mom spent a long time cooking this.
If you won't have it, then I will.
We brought back quite a lot of things.
You guys are amazing.
So much good food.
Let's split it half and half.
I don't know when
my son's leg will fully recover.
He can't work, and he's just a burden.
An old woman like me is useless, too.
When I make soup,
I can only find some wild vegetable leaves.
Just take it for now.
We can always find more later.
Thank you.
Thank you, young man.
You're all good people.
Eat up, eat up.
Hurry and eat.
What's the problem?
The fuel line is clogged.
Is it an easy fix?
It's not hard, it just takes time.
Come on, follow me to the eastern woods.
I still have to clear the fuel line.
I plan to leave tomorrow.
We need to stock up on food.
Tomorrow?
Then we should fix the boat even sooner.
How about this?
You go hunting, and I'll keep fixing it.
No.
We go together.
Why? You're enough for hunting on your own.
And you can't help with the boat.
You want to leave soon,
but you won't divide the work.
- What exactly do you want?
- I can't leave you alone.
It's dangerous.
Dangerous?
Lie.
I'm going with you,
but that doesn't mean I'm your prisoner.
I'm fixing the boat to help you, after all.
We don't have much time.
Let's not waste it keeping tabs on each other.
You're back.
This chicken is so fat.
Look, a chicken.
Are you going out again?
What took you so long?
What? Afraid I'll run away?
Madam.
We're having chicken tonight.
Your friend is really impressive.
We haven't had meat in a long time.
Your hands are dirty. Go wash up first.